Inventory of the American National Red Cross records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Commission for Belgium, 1914-1922
  - "Belgium War-Activities under the Minister of the Interior, Founded with the Cooperation of the American Red Cross," report by Minister of State High Commissioner of the Belgian Government, Former Minister of the Interior Paul Berryer, Paris, January 15, 1919
    Box/Folder30: 12. Original and translation
  - Material that went into report made for Major W.M. Bullett, 1919
    Box/Folder 30: 13-14
  - Home Communication Service, 1919. Includes Missing List and Requests for Details Death and Burial, #7, Paris, October 1, 1918
    Box/Folder 30: 15
  - Deputy Commissioner John Van Schaick Jr., reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 30: 16-17
  - General reports, 1918-1919 (Reel 44)
    Box/Folder 31: 1-3
  - Appropriation, 1919
    Box/Folder 31: 4
  - The Fourth Year in Belgium, by Paul U. Kellogg, Paris, 1919 (?)
    Box/Folder 31: 5
  - Earnest Bicknell and John Van Schaick, correspondence, 1919
    Box/Folder 31: 6-11
  - Earnest Bicknell and John Van Schaick, correspondence, 1919 (Reel 45)
    Box/Folder 31: 12
  - John Van Schaick, report to Finance Committee, 1917
    Box/Folder 31: 13
  - "Brief History of Commission for Belgium," by John Van Schaick, Jr., 1919
    Box/Folder 31: 14
  - John Van Schaick, articles, 1918
    Box/Folder 31: 15
  - Various offices and headquarters of American organizations, addresses, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 31: 16
  - General information, 1919
    Box/Folder 31: 17
  - Office Central d'Identification, Office Central d'Informations, Office de Renseignements des Oeuvres, 1914-1918, Brussels, reports, printed copy
    Box/Folder 31: 18
  - General correspondence, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 31: 19-21
  - Belgian officials correspondence, 1917-1920
    - Minister of Interior Paul Berryer, 1917-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 1-2
    - Minister of Finance Van der Vyvere, 1917-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 3
    - Minister of Foreign Affairs Paul Hymans, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 4
    - Minister of National Reconstruction Baron de Broqueville, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 5
    - Minister of War Général A. de Ceuninck, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 32: 6
    - Minister of Industry Joseph M. Wauters, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 7
    - Minister of Supplies Emile Vandervelde, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 8
    - American Minister to Belgium Brand Whitlock, 1918-1920
      Box/Folder 32: 9
  - Budget for the construction of Haut-Graville, a village for Belgian refugees, Ministry of Interior, 1918
    Box/Folder 32: 10-14
  - International Committee, 1918 (Reel 46)
    Box/Folder 32: 15
  - American Fund for French Wounded, weekly bulletin, Paris, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 32: 16
  - Committee of Red Cross Societies, bulletin no. 1, Paris, March 1919
    Box/Folder 32: 17
  - International Conference of Red Cross Societies in Geneva, 1919
    Box/Folder 32: 18
  - Personnel, 1918-1919
    - Directory, 1918
      Box/Folder 32: 19
    - Edwards A. Park, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 20
    - Mason J.H. Knox, 1918
      Box/Folder 32: 21
    - Leonard Chester Jones, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 22-23
    - Francis D. Mulvey, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 32: 24
    - Lee James Wideman, 1918
      Box/Folder 32: 25
    - Dr. Pilleboue, 1918
      Box/Folder 32: 26
    - William Caldwell Titcomb, 1918
      Box/Folder 32: 27
    - Julia Romaine Van Schaick, 1919
      Box/Folder 33: 1
    - Ernest P. Bicknell, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 33: 2
    - John W. Gummere, 1918
      Box/Folder 33: 3
  - Budget and appropriations, 1917-1920
    Box/Folder 33: 4-6
  - Monthly subsidies for Belgian organizations, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 33: 7
  - Appeals, 1921
    Box/Folder 33: 8
  - Child health, 1921
    Box/Folder 33: 9
  - Finance reports, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 33: 10
  - General relief, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 33: 11-14
  - France--General relief, Belgium Unit, 1919
    Box/Folder 33: 15
  - Liquidation operations, 1920
    Box/Folder 33: 16
  - Gifts for Belgian soldiers, 1917-1919 (Reel 47)
    Box/Folder 33: 17-19
  - Libraries for Belgian soldiers, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 33: 20
  - Official Belgian organizations, ledgers, 1917-1919
    - Cantine at Gare du Nord, Paris, 1917
      Box/Folder 33: 21
    - Le Foyer du Soldat Belge, bulletin, Paris, 1916-1918
      Box/Folder 33: 22-23
    - Le Congé du Soldat Belge, 1917-1919
      Box/Folder 33: 24
    - Home du Soldat Belge de la Petite Couronne, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 1
    - Hôpital Militaire Belge no. 8, Le Havre, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 34: 2
    - Restaurant Militaire de la Rue Mazagran, Paris, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 3
    - Cercle Sportif Belge du Havre, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 4
    - Little Belgian Soldiers' Club at Graville, 1918 (Reel 48)
      Box/Folder 34: 5
    - Symphonie Belge (Belgian Military Band), 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 6
    - Foyer du Soldat Belge, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 34: 7
    - La Famille de l'Infirmière (Convalescent Home for Belgian Military Nurses), 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 37: 8
    - Emergency canteens at Front, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 9
    - The Queen Purse Fund, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 34: 10
    - Le Fonds du Soldat Belge, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 11
    - Belgische Standaard, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 12
    - Educating the soldiers at the front, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 13
    - Centres de Récréation au Front Belge, 1918
      Box/Folder 34: 14
    - Fédération Nationale des Politiques de la Guerre, 1919
      Box/Folder 34: 15
    - Hôpital Militaire Belge (HMB), 1917-1919
      - General, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 34: 16
      - L'Ambulance de l'Océan à La Panne, 1917-1919
        Box/Folder 34: 17-18
      - Purchase of artificial limbs, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 34: 19
      - Mobil Surgical Section, 1917
        Box/Folder 34: 20
      - Le Montpellier (Hérault), 1918
        Box/Folder 34: 21
      - Soligny la Trappe (Orne), 1918
        Box/Folder 34: 22
      - Chambéry (Savoie), 1918
        Box/Folder 34: 23
      - Field Ambulance Hospital no. 58, 1918
        Box/Folder 34: 24
      - St. Jones et Anastasie at Cannes, 1918
        Box/Folder 34: 25
      - St. Camille, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 34: 26
      - Subsidy of 300,000 francs for supplies for HMB, 1918
        Box/Folder 34: 27
  - Military relief, 1918-1919
    - Service de Santé Belge, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 34: 28
    - Croix-Rouge de Belgique, 1918-1919 (Reel 49)
      Box/Folder 34: 29-30
    - Relief for American soldiers, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 34: 31-33
    - Mutilés, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 34: 34
  - Civilian relief, 1914-1919
    - Children, 1917-1919
      - Belgian children in France, 1917-1919
        - For creation of Colony of 1000 children from occupied Belgium, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 1
        - Personal Representative of Her Majesty the Queen of Belgium, Capitaine Charles Graux, correspondence re Children's Colonies (Queen's Schools), 1917-1919
          Box/Folder 35: 2-3
        - Personal Representative of Her Majesty the Queen of Belgium, Capitaine Charles Graux, correspondence re Children's Colonies (Queen's Schools), 1917-1919 (Reel 50)
          Box/Folder 35: 4-7
        - Ecole de St. Vallier and Val. Brian, Drôme, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 8
        - La Colonie Scolaire de Recques, Pas-de-Calais, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 9
        - General reports, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 35: 10
        - Milk question (cows), 1917
          Box/Folder 35: 11
        - Sewing and knitting machines for the Clothing Department, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 35: 12
        - Contribution for Christmas treats by ARC El Paso Chapter, Texas, 1917
          Box/Folder 35: 13
        - Crèche de Wulveringhem (Nursery), 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 14
        - Appropriation for bringing 600 children to France and Switzerland from places of danger in Belgium, October 13, 1917
          Box/Folder 35: 15
        - Colonie Scolaire de Leysele, 1918-1919 (Reel 51)
          Box/Folder 35: 16
        - Colonie Scolaire de Cayeux-sur-Mer, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 35: 17
        - Colonie Enfants de La Lys, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 18
        - Subsidy by Her Majesty Elisabeth, Queen of Belgium, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 19
        - Refuge for Belgian boys at Wizernes, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 20-22
        - Directeur du Pensionnat de Loudun, l'Abbé Delforge, 1918
          Box/Folder 35: 23
      - Belgian children in Switzerland, 1917-1918
        - Project for placing Belgian children in Switzerland, 1917
          Box/Folder 36: 1
        - Reports on the Belgian children cared for in Switzerland at the expense of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 36: 2-3
        - Inter office correspondence, reports, ledgers, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 36: 4-5
        - Inter office correspondence, reports, ledgers, 1917-1918 (Reel 52)
          Box/Folder 36: 6-7
        - Présidente, Comité de Secours aux Réfugiés Belges, Mary Widmer Curtat, correspondence, 1918
          Box/Folder 36: 8
      - Colonies under the Minister of Justice-- Royal Institution of Messines for the Daughters of Belgian Officers, 1917-1919
        Box/Folder 36: 9-10
      - Boy Scouts de Belgique, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 36: 11
      - Les Petites Roses de la Reine, 1919
        Box/Folder 36: 12
      - Work of Jeanne de Ponthière at Liège, 1919
        Box/Folder 36: 13
      - Special gifts for children, 1918-1920
        Box/Folder 36: 14
      - Oeuvre de la Protection Maternelle et Infantile (Health Center for Babies at Le Havre), 1917-1918
        - Correspondence re: opening the Health Center, 1917
          Box/Folder 36: 15
        - Dispensary report, 1918
          Box/Folder 36: 16-17
        - "The Hospital, The Training School for Nurses' Aids, Consultation for Normal Infants," reports, 1918
          Box/Folder 36: 18
        - General correspondence, 1918-1919.
          Box/Folder 36: 19-21. Includes some reports
        - Weekly and monthly reports, 1918-1919
          Box/Folder 36: 22
        - Weekly and monthly reports, 1918-1919 (Reel 53)
        - ARC report of dispensary and hospital work among children at the Sally Franklin, Le Havre, January 1918 to May 1918
          Box/Folder 36: 24-25
        - Dr. Walter R. Ramsey, correspondence, 1918-1919
          Box/Folder 37: 1
        - Work for children in connection with the Queen of Belgium, 1918-1919
          Box/Folder 37: 2
      - La Pouponnière des Etablissements d'Artillerie de Graville, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 37: 3
      - Le Directeur de l'Institut Royal pour Sourds-Muets et Aveugles Père Libert, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 37: 4
      - Crèche du Nord-Est, Bruxelles, 1919
        Box/Folder 37: 5
      - Crèche Belge, Bruxelles, 1919
        Box/Folder 37: 6
      - Tribunal des Enfants, Bruxelle, 1919
        Box/Folder 37: 7
      - Société Protectrice des Enfants Martyrs, 1919.
        Box/Folder 37: 8. Includes report, 1912
      - Notre Abri, Asile pour les Tout Petits, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 37: 9
      - Belgian societies, 1917-1919
        - Ligue Nationale pour la Protection de l'Enfance, 1917
          Box/Folder 37: 10
        - Comité des Jeux et Récréations pour les Ecoliers Belges, 1918
          Box/Folder 37: 11
        - Madame E. de Ladrier, work for children, 1918-1919
          Box/Folder 37: 12
        - Cardinal Mercier, work for children, 1918-1919
          Box/Folder 37: 13
        - Le Foyer des Orphelins, 1918-1919
          Box/Folder 37: 14
        - Oeuvre Havraise des Crèches, 1918
          Box/Folder 37: 15
        - Association Nationale des Orphelins de la Guerre, 1918
          Box/Folder 37: 16
    - Colonies Scolaires du Ministère de l'Intérieur, 1917-1919
      - M. Dom, Directeur Général du Ministère de l'Intérieur, 1918
        Box/Folder 37: 17
      - Sénateur Empain, director of the Paris Group, Paris, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 37: 18-19
      - Ecole Sainte-Barbe, Fontenay-sur Roses, 1918
        Box/Folder 37: 20
      - St Jacques-sur-Darnetal, Orphanage of Locre, Major Clopton
        Box/Folder 37: 21
      - M. Olbrecht, director of the Normandy Group, 1918
        Box/Folder 37: 22
      - Saint-Illiers-le-Bois, 1918
        Box/Folder 37: 23
      - Yvetot, undated
        Box/Folder 37: 24
      - La Voltère, 1918
        Box/Folder 37: 25
      - Oeuvre de la Croix-Mauve, 1918.
        Box/Folder 37: 26. Includes photographic postcards
    - Hospitals, 1917-1919
      - Cardinal Mercier, 1918
        Box/Folder 37: 27
      - Civilian Hospital at Ebblinghem, near Hazerbrouck (for typhoid), 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 37: 28
      - L'Hôpital Civil du Havre, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 37: 29
      - Contesse Van den Steen, 1917-1918 (Reel 54)
        Box/Folder 37: 30
      - L'Hôpital Civil de la Chartreuse, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 38: 1
      - L'Hôpital Civil Belge Dorntje, Leysele, 1918
        Box/Folder 38: 2
      - L'Hôpital Civil, Lumbres, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 38: 3
      - L'Hôpital Civil de Job, 1918.
        Box/Folder 38: 4.Includes postcards
      - Belgian Civilian Tuberculosis Hospital at Chanay, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 38: 5
      - Maternity Hospital at Housbrugge, 1918
        Box/Folder 38: 6
      - Hospices Civils, Ville de Thielt, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 38: 7
      - La Clinique Médicale de l'Université de Liège, 1919
        Box/Folder 38: 8
      - L'Université Libre de Bruxelles, 1919
        Box/Folder 38: 9
      - Tuberculosis in Belgium, reports, 1912-1919
        Box/Folder 38: 10-12
      - Refugees, 1914-1919
        - Comité Officiel Belge de Secours aux Réfugiés, correspondence with Representatives, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 38: 13-14. Includes reports from various arrondissements
        - Comité Officiel Belge de Secours aux Réfugiés, correspondence with Representatives, 1917-1918
          Box/Folder 38: 15-21
        - Belgian refugee service, 1917-1918 (Reel 55)
          Box/Folder 38: 22. Contains field reports
        - Clothing section, accounting, reports, letters of thanks, 1918-1919 (Reel 56)
          Box/Folder 39: 1-15
        - Oeuvre de la Layette Belge, 1917-1919 (Reel 57)
          Box/Folder 39: 16
        - Vestiaire Marie-José, 1918
          Box/Folder 39: 17
      - Habillement du Soldat Réformé, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 40: 1
      - Headquarters, Friends' Ambulance Unit (FAU), British Expeditionary Force, 1914-1918
        - Assistance in evacuation work, 1918
          Box/Folder 40: 2-4
        - Civil relief work for Dunkerque, 1914-1918
          Box/Folder 40: 5
        - Reports, 1914-1918
          Box/Folder 40: 6-8
        - A Story of the Work of the Friends' Ambulance Unit, by Geoffrey Winthrop Young, 1915
          Box/Folder 40: 9
        - Milk distribution, 1918
          Box/Folder 40: 10
        - Queen Alexandra Hospital, 1918
          Box/Folder 40: 11
      - Belgian Civil Hospital no. 2, Courtrai, 1918
        Box/Folder 40: 12
      - Foyer Ecosse Ryfe, Georgia, 1918
        Box/Folder 40: 13
      - Commissaire d'Arrondissement Jean de Furnes Steynert, Furnes, Belgique, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 40: 14
      - Emergency relief work, 1918
        Box/Folder 40: 15
      - Commissaire d'Arrondissement de Bruges, Coppieters't Wallant, Robert, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 40: 16
      - Comité Officiel Belge de Secours aux Réfugiés, 1917-1918
        - General correspondence, memorandum, reports, 1917-1919
          Box/Folder 40: 17-19
        - President of l'Union Belge at Elbeuf M. Jaupard, correspondence, 1918
          Box/Folder 40: 20. Includes reports and newspaper clippings
        - L'Union Amicale des Réfugiés Belges, reports, 1917
          Box/Folder 40: 21
        - Clermont-Ferrand District, 1918
          Box/Folder 40: 22
      - Comité National de Secours et d'Alimentation, correspondence, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 40: 23. Includes scheme of organization
      - Village de Haut Graville pour Réfugiés Belges--Construction of provisional dwellings, 1918-1919 (Reel 58)
        Box/Folder 41: 1. See also map case for the drawings
      - Reports on living conditions in Le Havre, 1917
        Box/Folder 41: 2
      - Milk supplies for refugees at Le Havre, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 3
      - Refugee Center at Rouen, correspondence, reports, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 41: 4
      - Permanence des Réfugiés à Rouen, 1916-1918
        Box/Folder 41: 5
      - Comité Municipal des Réfugiés au Havre, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 6
      - Cantine de l'Agence Maritime, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 41: 7
      - Syndicat des Travailleuses de l'Aiguille (for Belgian women), Le Havre, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 8
      - Appui Belge, the Belgian Aid, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 9
      - Le Comité Central Franco-Belge, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 41: 10
      - Assistance aux Bombardés Civils, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 41: 11
      - Barracks for Belgiun--Work of Roland Hyman at La Panne, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 12-13
      - Comité Dentellier Belgo-Franco-Américain, organization, statements, correspondence, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 41: 14
      - Institut Militaire des Invalides et Orphelins de la Guerre, correspondence, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 15
      - Oeuvre du Travail Agricole à Pontoise, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 16
      - Oeuvre du Travail Agricole à Pontoise, 1918 (Reel 59)
        Box/Folder 41: 17
      - Joseph Fabre, Aumônier des Flottilles de Patrouilles, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 18
      - M. Van der Chote, Infirmière Principale de la Section Belge, Hôpital Militaire le Garage, St. Lunaire, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 19
      - Oeuvre de l'Assistance Temporaire aux Belges, correspondence, reports, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 41: 20-22
      - Abbé Corty, Albi--Refugee work, 1918
        Box/Folder 41: 23
    - Fonds du Roi Albert, 1917-1919
      - Correspondence, 1917-1919
        Box/Folder 42: 1
      - Reports, 1917-1919
        Box/Folder 42: 2-4
      - Reports, 1917-1919 (Reel 60)
        Box/Folder 42: 5-7
      - Minutes of meetings, 1917-1919
        Box/Folder 42: 8-11
    - Centrale d'Oeuvres Sociales pour les Réfugiés Belges, 1918-1919 (Reel 61)
      Box/Folder 42: 12-13
    - Comité Belge du Travail à Domicile, London, 1918
      Box/Folder 42: 14
    - Relief for Belgian Prisoners in Germany, 1918
      Box/Folder 42: 15
    - Clothing of Belgian Destitute Civilians, London, 1918
      Box/Folder 42: 16
    - Bureau Belge des Réfugiés Belges, London, 1918
      Box/Folder 43: 1
    - Comité des Visiteurs aux Blessés Belges, London, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 43: 2
    - Relief refugees in Holland, 1917-1919
      - General, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 3
      - Le Phalanstère Belge, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 43: 4-6
      - Oeuvre de la Santé à l'Enfance, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 7. Includes photographs of children
      - Home des Petits Orphelins de la Guerre, correspondence, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 8. Includes photographs of children
      - Belgian Children's Milk Fund and its Branch Home for Little Belgian Orphans (Oeuvre Belge du Lait pour les Petits), reports, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 9
      - Ecole Belge La Haye, reports, 1914-1915
        Box/Folder 43: 10
      - Home des Internés Belges à La Haye, report, undated
        Box/Folder 43: 11. See also oversized box 223
      - Institut und Kloster Mariazell, album, undated
        Box/Folder 43: 12
      - Comité d'Assistance aux Belges, report, 1918 (Reel 62)
        Box/Folder 43: 13
      - Association des Dames Visitant les Familles d'Internés, report, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 14
      - Home pour les Sinistrés Belges de la Guerre, report, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 15
      - La Ruche, Oeuvre Anglo-Belge, The Hague, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 43: 16
      - Fund for Belgian Soldiers Interned in Holland, Office Central Belge, Le Havre, correspondence, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 43: 17-18. Includes Project de Construction d'Hôpital, 1918
    - Secours aux Infortunés de la Guerre, London, correspondence, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 43: 19
    - California House for Disabled Belgian Soldiers, London, correspondence, reports, prints, 1915-1919
      Box/Folder 43: 20
    - Refugees' relief in Belgium, 1918-1919
      - General, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 21
      - The Commission for Relief in Belgium, London, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 22
      - ARC Fund for Relief in Belgium, correspondence, reports, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 23
      - The Belgian Doctors' and Pharmacists' Relief Fund, London, reports, correspondence, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 24
      - Baron Gilles de Pélichy's work in Flanders, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 25
      - Comité de Secours et d'Alimentation, Aeltre, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 26
      - Ostende Fishing Project, report, 1918
        Box/Folder 43: 27
      - L'Association de la Presse Belge, correspondence, reports, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 44: 1
      - Oeuvre de l'Assistance Discrète, correspondence, printed reports, 1917-1918
        Box/Folder 44: 2-3
      - Cardinal Mercier, work for refugees, 1918
        Box/Folder 44: 4
      - Refugees return home from England, France and Holland, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 44: 5
      - Construction of 50 houses at Termonde, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 44: 6
      - Soeur Marie Joséphine, Furnes, 1919
        Box/Folder 44: 7
      - Locating families, correspondence, 1919
        Box/Folder 44: 8
      - Official correspondence, 1918-1919
        Box/Folder 44: 9-10
- Commission for Great Britain, 1917-1921
  - American Library Association, Library War Service, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 11
  - American Red Cross Bulletin, London, 1918 (Reel 63)
    Box/Folder 44: 12
  - ARC Care Committee for Soldiers and Sailors, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 13
  - Activities of ARC at Aviation Camps, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 14
  - Appreciation letters, Wales, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 44: 15-16
  - Bishop Charles H. Brent request for books for Chaplains' School, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 17
  - Canteen Service, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 44: 18-19
  - Camp Service Bureau, organization, orders, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 20
  - Red Cross Chaplains, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 21
  - Amesbury Depot, report of operations, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 22
  - Home Communication Department, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 23
  - British Base Hospitals in France, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 44: 24
  - Convalescent Hospital no. 1, Ford Manor, Lingfield, Surrey, 1918
    Box/Folder 44: 25
  - Military Hospital no. 22 (for officers), Lancaster Gate, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 44: 26
  - St. Katherine's Lodge Hospital. Includes special financial report, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 44: 27-28
  - The Coldra, Hospital for American Troops, correspondence, reports, architectural drawings, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 45: 1
  - The Coldra, Hospital for American Troops, correspondence, reports, architectural drawings, 1918-1919 (Reel 64)
    Box/Folder 45: 2
  - U.S. Navy Hospital no. 25 (Aldford House), correspondence, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 45: 3-4
  - ARC Paris Headquarters, reports to, 1917
    Box/Folder 45: 5
  - The Montenegrin Red Cross and Relief Fund to ARC, 1918
    Box/Folder 45: 6
  - Publicity, 1918
    Box/Folder 45: 7
  - Troops' supplies (from ARC), 1917
    Box/Folder 45: 8
  - Tuscania and Otranto catastrophe victims and Islay Monument, 1918
    Box/Folder 45: 9-11
  - Venereal diseases, reports, Press Bulletin, A.L.A., War Service, Library of Congress, Washington, D.C., 1918
    Box/Folder 45: 12
  - ARC--Agreement with YMCA regarding recreation work in the military hospitals, 1918